Mirlan Nurbekov

Software engineer

I am a well-educated software engineer with strong knowledge and experience in project and event management, boasting nearly seven years of working experience in an international environment. As a software engineer I am skilled in programming, building complex queries, stored procedures and functions, coordinating complex schedules, managing essential administrative tasks, projects, and facilitating effective communication across diverse cultural environments. I am fluent in English and Russian, demonstrating proficiency in translating official documents and engaging in multilingual interactions.



mirlan96nurbekov@gmail.com

Bishkek, Kyrgyzstan

in linkedin.com/in/mirlan-nurbekov

+996551999747

mirlan-nurbekov-portfolio-website.vercel.app

github.com/MirlanNurbekov

WORK EXPERIENCE

International College of IT and Business Salymbekov University

Web Development Lecturer

01/2024 - Present Bishkek, Kyrgyzstan

The International College of IT and Business "Salymbekov University" is a new college with a modern material and technical base designed to provide training for specialists in the latest training program in Russian and English.

Zentrek Technologies Sdn

Role - Software engineer (5 years)

01/2019 - 06/2023

Penang, Malaysia

Zentrek Technologies Sdn Bhd is a comprehensive IT company that has been providing a wide range of IT services for the past 20 years. Specializing in both hardware and software development, the company caters to diverse technological needs and continues to innovate and expand its offerings in the IT sector.

Cincaria Sdn Bhd

Role - Electronic Engineer (2 years)

01/2017 - 01/2019

Penang, Malaysia

Cincaria Sdn Bhd is a well-established and reputable electro-mechanical and electronics contract manufacturer, founded in 1997 in Penang, Malaysia.

EDUCATION &

Bachelor of Science (Hons) Computing & IT Coventry University, UK

07/2018 - 03/2021

Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia

Diploma in Electrical and Electronic Engineering

INTI International University & College Penang

07/2015 - 07/2017 Penang, Malaysia

TECHNICAL SKILLS

C# C++ JavaScript SQL ASP.Net MVC

React Unity Blender 3D Debugging

ACHIEVEMENTS

1st place in JABIL GBS Competition "LEADING THE DIGITAL FUTURE" Penang, Malaysia (09/2022)

Role - Team leader

2nd place in INTI-USC Competition in the Business Service Sector Penang, Malaysia (11/2021)

Role - App developer

Outstanding Contribution Award as a Student Ambassador in INTI Penang, Malaysia (03/2016 - 12/2021)

• Role - Student Ambassador

LANGUAGES

ENGLISH

RUSSIAN

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

KYRGYZ

Limited Working Proficiency

SOFT SKILLS

Problem-Solving Communication Teamwork

Adaptability Time Management

Analytical Thinking Customer Service

Time Management Public speaking

Critical thinking